costingdecrease.com 2014-09-10

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement

We highly value the privacy of all individuals and users. All information we collect is used to provide you with information on relevant products and services and to improve our level of service to our users. Your data will be handled in accordance with the provisions of both the EU and US national laws and regulations. Your information will not be disclosed to any source other than this website, its subsidiaries and distributors.

How we use personal information:

Personal data can be used:

1> According to your privacy settings, freely released by you

2> Depending on your settings, allowing you to use as many site features as possible

3> To perform customer service and management

4> To serve relevant and superior products and services to you

5> To serve relevant and more natural advertising

6> For investigation of fraud and violations of our Terms of Use

Cookie Usage

Cookies are small amounts of data stored on the user’s computer. If you accept cookies, cookies will be sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to track your use on our site, so that when you visit again, we can identify you and analyze your previous use to provide better service for you. You have the option to accept or reject cookies. You can modify your browser settings to refuse to accept cookies, but we need to remind you, if you refuse to accept cookies, some features of the site may not work as intended. 

Information collected

This website may collect your personal information or information obtained from third parties to provide you with better customer service. This website uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to understand your use of the site. When you visit our website or use some of our products, the site's servers automatically record information, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of use. When you visit our site, we will be advertising through third-party advertising companies. These companies may use information about your visit (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) in order to show you products and services that you may be interested in.

Security

Please note that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. To prevent the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction, we will take reasonable steps to protect all information. In particular,
